

# PONJEVIC **GORAN**Web developer

Beograd, Novi Beograd

☑ ponjevic.goran@hotmail.com

**\&** +381 66 166 006

## SOCIAL

in goran-ponjevic

minnuss /

goran.ponjevic

## PROFILE

Hi, I'm Goran. I have a 10+ years of experience in administration and IT support. I am outgoing, dedicated, open-minded. I believe that a person should work on developing their professional skills and learning new things all the time. Currently, I'm looking for new career opportunities in Web Development.

# EDUCATION

Masinski Tehnicar
Tehnička škola "Novi Beograd"
1997 - 2000

## SKILLS

- Html
- MS Navision
- CSS
- Ubuntu
- Sass
- JIRA
- JavaScript
- Git
- SEO on page

#### EXPERIENCE

# ADMINISTRATION & IT SUPPORT

From 2005 to 2021 | Fortuna Int.

Worked in MS Dynamics Navision, creating and inserting data (articles, descriptions, customers, manipulating images), processing orders, making offers, taking care of goods logistics.

Analyzing various data and generating reports.

Managing GPS tracking software.

Troubleshooting IT problems, hardware, software, and network related. Installing and maintaining computers and other devices in company.

## MILITARY SERVICE

From 2002 to 2003 | Prištinski korpus

Military service in Prištinski korpus, city of Vranje.

## PC HARDWARE TRADING

From 2001 to 2002 | Cedens Co.

Selling pc components.

Assembling desktop PCs.

Testing hardware, installing OS, drivers and software.

## REFERENCES

Selling natural sweets

Music studio

koliko.rs

ponksound.rs

Email: quince@koliko.rs

Email: info@ponksound.com

#### LANGUAGES

English

Serbian

## INTERESTS

4H)

00,

٩

Music

**Fitness** 

Movies

Technology

Networking